Equal Justice USA; Records apap358
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York Press, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
- New York Press Packets, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- New York State Files, 2004-2005; Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
- New York Times "Electric Chair" Ad, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Nichols, Terry, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- NJ Death Penally Study Commission Report, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- NJ Postcard, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Newsletters, Justice in the Works, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Newsletters Moratorium News, 1997-2005; 2007-2012 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- No Greater Pain, Undated (Dvd 5)
- North Carolina (1 of 3), 1998-2004; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- North Carolina (2 of 3), 1998-2004; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- North Carolina (1 of 3), 1998-2004; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- North Carolinians Against the Death Penalty, 1998 (Video-tape 9)
- North Dakota, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Northeast Field Office, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Notes from Talks, 1992-1994; 1996-1997; 2000-2001; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Notes of Appreciation, 2001-2002; 2004-2005; 2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Nuclear Freeze Background, 1997; 2000; Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NUVO, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- "NUVO" (Indiana), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- NY Ad Mailing, 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- NYADP Senate Poll, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- NYC Gradess Hebrew Tabernacle, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- NY Legislative Hearings on Death Penalty (1 of 4), 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- NY Legislative Hearings on Death Penalty (2 of 4), 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- NY Legislative Hearings on Death Penalty (3 of 4), 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- NY Legislative Hearings on Death Penalty (4 of 4), 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- NYT Ad, 1999; Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
- O'Pell, Joseph, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Ohio (1 of 2), 1992; 1997-2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Ohio (1 of 2), 1992; 1997-2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Ohioans to Stop Executions, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Ohio Death Penalty Assessment Report, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- One for Ten, Undated (Dvd 6)
- One More Voice, 1998 (Video-tape 10)
- Oklahoma, 1998-2011; Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Oregon, 1998-1999; 2000; Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Organizing Guides, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Outside In, Undated (Cd 26)
- Paradise Lost 3: Purgatory, 2011 (Dvd 7)
- Pennsylvania (1 of 4), 1992-1993; 1995; 1998-2004; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania (2 of 4), 1992-1993; 1995; 1998-2004; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania (3 of 4), 1992-1993; 1995; 1998-2004; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania (4 of 4), 1992-1993; 1995; 1998-2004; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Pennsylvania Executions (1 of 2), 1992-1994; 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Executions (2 of 2), 1992-1994; 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Police Forum on the Death Penalty, Undated (Cd 27)
- Police Misconduct, 1996; 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Polls Public Opinion, 1981; 1991; 1997; 1999-2001; Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Post-911, 2001-2003; Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Porten, Anthony, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Post-Moratorium, 2002-2006; Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Press, 1983; 1987; 1999-2000; 2005; 2007 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Press Clips, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Press, Maryland Moratorium, 2000-2002; Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Press Packet, 1996; Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Prison Industrial, 1980; 1990; 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Prison Labor, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Public Executions Figures, 1996-1997; 2012-2013; Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Queens Update: A Live Town Hall Meeting, Undated (Cd 28)
- Race, 1990; 1995; 1997-1998; 2004; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Race to Execution, Undated (Dvd 8)
- Racial Disparity, 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Racial Justice Act, 1990-1991; 1994; Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Redemption, 2004 (Video-tape 11)
- Reducing Death Sentences, 2007; Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Reeues, Randy, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Refocusing the Death Penalty Discussion in America, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Reform, 2003; 2009; Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Regional, 1997-1998; 2000-2002; Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Religious Views on Death Penalty, 1990; 1997-1998; 2004; Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Resolution Originals, 1997-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Restorative Justice, 2003; 2005; Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Rethinking the Death Penalty, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rhode Island, 1999; 2000; Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Richie, Kenny, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Robert Alton Harris Video, Undated (Video-tape 12)
- Saga, 1998; Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Saga, Articles Received, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Saga, Case Studies, 1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Saga, Conference Call Minutes, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Saga, Conference Committee Letters of Invitation, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Saga, Confirmed Writers, ca. 1997/1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Saga Contract, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Saga Info, 1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Saga Info, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Saga of Shame Proposal, Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Saga Potential Writers, 1991; 1995; 1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Saga Projects, 1996; Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Saga: To Conference Call Committee, 1998 February 2 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Second Annual March for a Moratorium and Abolitionist of the Year Photos, Undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Sentencing Alternatives, 1982; 1988; 1992; Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Shakur, Shaka, 1992; Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Shepard Case, 1999; Undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Sheppard Sam, 1995; 1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Simpson, O.J., 1994; 1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Social Form Mortarium Workshop, 2007; Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
- South Carolina, 1998-2000; 2002; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
- South Dakota, 1999; 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Southeast Field Office, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Staff Meetings, 2009; 2011 (Flat-file 1)
- State by State Edition, 2002; Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- State by State Trends, 1999; Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- State Polls, 1994; 2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- States Abolish the Death Penalty, 2007; 2009; 2012 (Flat-file 2)
- Stop the Politics of Fear, 1996 (Cd 29)
- Summary of Moratorium Resolution Impacts, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Support the NC Racial Justice Act, Undated (Cd 30)
- Tablecloth Workshop, 2003; Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Tennessee (1 of 2), 2000-2006; Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Tennessee (2 of 2), 2000-2006; Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Tennessee Death Penalty Assessment Report, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Testimony on Death Penalty Bill, 2008 (Cd 31)
- Testimony of John Dunne at Joint Public Hearings on the Death Penalty, Undated (Cd 32)
- Texas (1 of 3), 1997-2013; Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Texas (2 of 3), 1997-2013; Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Texas (3 of 3), 1997-2013; Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Thank You Postcard, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- The Confessions, 2010 (Dvd 9)
- The Empty Chair, 2003 (Dvd 10)
- The Execution Tapes, 2002 (Cd 33)
- The Exonerated Court TV, Undated (Cd 34)
- Thomas M. Cooley Law Review, 2005 International Leadership Conference on Human Rights and the Death Penalty, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Time Out: Perspectives on New Jersey's Death Penalty, 2002 (Video-tape 13)
- Too Flawed to Fix:, Undated (Video-tape 14)
- To Shai With Love, Undated (Cd 35)
- Transition Info, 2006; 2008; Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Training Retreat, 2003; 2006-2007; Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Tribunal Discussion on Lethal Injection in Missouri, Undated (Cd 36)
- Tucker, Karla Faye, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- TV Ad Campaign, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Unified Death Penalty Strategy Retreat, 2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Unitarian Universalists for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 1998; 2005; Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
- United States and International, 1999; Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Unusual Suspects, 2000; 2006 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Urgent Action Direct Mail, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Utah, 2000; 2010; Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Virginia Moratorium Campaign Materials, 2005; Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Vermont, 1998; 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Victims, General, 1991; 2002; 2006; Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Victim Info Files, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Victims, Secondary Trauma, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Viginia (1 of 5), 1992; 1998-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Viginia (2 of 5), 1992; 1998-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Viginia (3 of 5), 1992; 1998-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Viginia (4 of 5), 1992; 1998-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Viginia (5 of 5), 1992; 1998-2003; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Vision, 2000; Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Washington, 1998-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Washington, D.C., 1998-2001; 2010; Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Website Redesigns, 2010; Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
- West Virginia, 1998; 1999; 2000; Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Who Bombed Judi Bari, Undated (Cd 37)
- Williamson, Ronald Fritz, Dennis, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Willie Simmons vs. State of Missouri (1 of 2), Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Willie Simmons vs. State of Missouri (2 of 2), Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Winter Communications, 2003; Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Wisconsin, 1998-2001; Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Women, 1990-1993; 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Wong, David, 1993; Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
- World Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Writings by Prisoners, 1997; Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Wyoming, 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)